The death toll is at 5 with 34 injured in the fire
‫بلغ عدد القتلى خمسة قتلى و34 جريحًا في حريق‬
at the Fredrich Emmanuel Library at Munich University.
‫قد اندلع في مكتبة "فريدريك إيمانويل"‬ ‫في جامعة "ميونخ".‬
A grueling search for the missing is still underway.
‫لا يزال البحث المضني عن المفقودين جاريًا.‬
We had a chance to speak with some of the survivors. Let's take a look.
‫سنحت لنا الفرصة‬ ‫للتحدث إلى بعض الناجين. لنلق نظرة.‬
Before I knew what was happening, we were surrounded by flames.
‫قبل أن أدرك ما يحدث،‬ ‫كانت النار قد أحاطت بنا.‬
The place was filled with smoke and I couldn't breathe.
‫امتلأ المكان بالدخان وعجزت عن التنفس.‬
I thought I was a goner.
‫ظننت أنني هالكة.‬
A man saved us. He was an Asian man.
‫أنقذنا رجل. كان أسيويًا.‬
Is he all right?
‫أهو بخير؟‬
He shot the door hinges with his gun and opened the door for us!
‫أطلق النار على مفصلات الباب بمسدسه‬ ‫وفتح الباب لنا!‬
If it weren't for him, a lot more people would have died.
‫لولاه، لمات عدد أكبر من الناس.‬
The police have determined
‫توصلت الشرطة‬
that this fire was deliberately set with kerosene and gasoline.
‫إلى أن هذا الحريق‬ ‫أُشعل عمدًا بالكيروسين والبنزين.‬
They've announced that they're doing everything possible to find the arsonist.
‫أعلنت الشرطة أنها تبذل قصارى جهدها‬ ‫للتوصل إلى من أشعل الحريق.‬
It's been burned to ashes.
‫تحوّلت إلى رماد.‬
I guess all this human wisdom doesn't amount to much when it's all burned up.
‫أرى أن الحكمة الإنسانية‬ ‫لا يصبح لها قيمة عند حرقها.‬
Any fingerprints on the sniper rifle that was found?
‫هل عُثر على بصمات على بندقية القنص؟‬
I doubt we'll find any after it's been through this fire.
‫أشك في أن نجد أي بصمات بعدما احترقت.‬
But it is definitely a Mauser SR93, just like the one bought by
‫لكنها بلا شك بندقية "ماوزر إس آر 93"،‬ ‫كالتي اشتراها‬
the Japanese man thought to be Dr. Tenma.
‫الياباني الذي يُشتبه في كونه د. "تينما".‬
After a fire like this, it's unlikely we'll find a trace of the arsonist.
‫من غير المحتمل أن نجد أثرًا لمشعل الحريق‬ ‫بعد حريق كهذا.‬
Every crime scene has evidence.
‫ما من مسرح جريمة يخلو من أدلة.‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
Here's a cufflink.
‫هاك زر كُم.‬
Have it analyzed.
‫حلّله.‬
Oh, okay.
‫حسنًا.‬
Someone was here.
‫كان ثمة أحد هنا.‬
There's not a human around
‫ما من إنسان‬
who can be somewhere without leaving a trace of their presence.
‫قد يذهب إلى مكان ولا يترك أثرًا له فيه.‬
If they can do that, then they're not human.
‫إن استطاع فعل ذلك، فلن يكون إنسانًا.‬
But if by chance they didn't leave any trace, then what are they?
‫لكن في حال لم يترك أثرًا له، فماذا سيكون؟‬
A demon.
‫شيطان.‬
But those don't exist in this world.
‫لكن ما من شياطين في عالمنا.‬
Therefore, anyone who commits a crime can be arrested.
‫لذلك كلّ من يرتكب جريمة، يمكن اعتقاله.‬
Can I speak with Schuwald?
‫أيمكنني التحدث إلى "شوفالد"؟‬
He's in intensive care now.
‫إنه في العناية المركزة الآن.‬
His burns weren't that bad,
‫لم تكن حروقه بهذا السوء،‬
but considering his age, they've decided not to allow visitors.
‫لكن نظرًا لتقدمه في العمر،‬ ‫فإنهم قرّروا منع زيارته.‬
-Let's talk to him. -Huh?
‫- لنتحدّث إليه.‬ ‫- ماذا؟‬
I cannot allow this!
‫لا يمكنني السماح بهذا.‬
I cannot let you see him!
‫لن أسمح لك بمقابلته!‬
He's conscious, right? We'll be through in a matter of minutes.
‫إنه واع، أليس كذلك؟‬ ‫سننهي حديثنا إليه في غضون دقائق.‬
Mr. Schuwald is in an extreme state of shock!
‫تعرّض السيد "شوفالد" لصدمة نفسية عنيفة!‬
He must rest for the time being.
‫يجب أن يرتاح في الوقت الحالي.‬
Who's that?
‫من ذلك؟‬
That's Mr. Schuwald's son.
‫إنه ابن السيد "شوفالد".‬
I'm sorry about what happened to your father.
‫يؤسفني ما حدث لوالدك.‬
I'm Lunge from the BKA.
‫أنا "لونغي"‬ ‫من مكتب الشرطة الجنائية الفيدرالية.‬
I told the police earlier that there was someone
‫أخبرت الشرطة سابقًا بأن ثمة شخص‬
I want them to look for.
‫أريدهم أن يبحثوا عنه.‬
Who's this?
‫من يكون هذا؟‬
He's the man who tried to assassinate your father.
‫إنه الرجل الذي حاول اغتيال والدك.‬
You honestly don't know him?
‫ألا تعرفه حقًا؟‬
No, I don't. But he might.
‫لا أعرفه. لكنه قد يعرفه.‬
Who's "he"?
‫من تقصد؟‬
That's what I wanted to tell you!
‫هذا ما أردت قوله لك!‬
You've got to find Johan Liebert!
‫يجب أن تجد "يوهان ليبرت".‬
Johan Liebert…
‫"يوهان ليبرت"…‬
Johan was also at the ceremony with my father!
‫كان "يوهان" في الحفل مع أبي أيضًا!‬
But I can't find him anywhere.
‫لكنني أعجز عن إيجاده في أي مكان.‬
Johan.
‫"يوهان".‬
Johan Liebert.
‫"يوهان ليبرت".‬
All right. We'll start searching for him right away.
‫حسنًا. سنبدأ في البحث عنه في الحال.‬
This is the place that Johan Liebert was renting.
‫هذا هو المكان‬ ‫الذي كان يستأجره "يوهان ليبرت".‬
He moved out about two weeks ago.
‫انتقل منه قبل أسبوعين.‬
There was no record of him at the law school.
‫لم يكن له سجل في كلية الحقوق.‬
He wasn't really a student.
‫لم يكن طالبًا.‬
Have you contacted his parents who live in Offenbach?
‫هل تواصلت مع والديه‬ ‫الذين يقيمان في "أوفنباخ"؟‬
That was a dead end as well.
‫كان ذلك طريقًا مسدودًا هو الآخر.‬
They are almost rarely spoke with neighbors.
‫نادرًا ما يتحدّثان إلى جيرانهما.‬
Do you want us to dust this place for fingerprints?
‫أتريدنا أن نبحث عن بصمات في هذا المكان؟‬
-I doubt you'll find any. -What?
‫- أشك في أن تجد شيئًا.‬ ‫- ماذا؟‬
No record of his presence.
‫ما من سجلات تثبت أن له وجودًا.‬
I've never seen anything like this.
‫لم أر شيئًا كهذا من قبل.‬
This place feels as if nobody has ever lived here.
‫يبدو المكان هنا كما لو أنه لم يعش فيه أحد.‬
Yeah.
‫أجل.‬
I am Johan.
‫أنا "يوهان".‬
I am Johan Liebert.
‫أنا "يوهان ليبرت".‬
Who am I?
‫من أكون؟‬
I was here.
‫كنت هنا.‬
But I don't exist.
‫لكنني غير موجود.‬
Am I a demon?
‫هل أنا شيطان؟‬
I'm sorry for making you worry about me, Lotte.
‫أعتذر عمّا أشعرتك به من قلق عليّ.‬
You better believe I was worried.
‫يُستحسن بك أن يكون هذا ما تصوّرته عني.‬
They kept pulling people out of there, but you never came out.
‫استمروا في إخراج الناس من هناك‬ ‫لكنك لم تخرجي.‬
I was so afraid for you.
‫خفت عليك بشدة.‬
With those injuries, I'm surprised you made it out of that fire on your own.
‫بإصاباتك هذه، تفاجأت من تمكنك من الخروج‬ ‫من ذلك الحريق وحدك.‬
The firemen were surprised too.
‫تفاجأ رجال الإطفاء أيضًا.‬
Someone helped me.
‫ثمة من ساعدني.‬
Someone helped you?
‫ثمة من ساعدك؟‬
You were the last person to come out, you know.
‫كنت آخر من خرج من هناك.‬
A Japanese man…
‫رجل ياباني…‬
Wasn't a Japanese doctor taken to one of the hospitals?
‫ألم يُؤخذ طبيبًا يابانيًا‬ ‫إلى إحدى المستشفيات؟‬
There were several Japanese people,
‫كان ثمة العديد من اليابانيين،‬
but I think they were all businessmen.
‫لكنني أظن أنهم كانوا رجال أعمال.‬
That's not possible.
‫غير معقول.‬
Really?
‫حقًا؟‬
You see, I was trapped beneath a curtain when he found me…
‫كنت عالقة تحت ستارة عندما وجدني…‬
Nina!
‫"نينا"!‬
I'm sure of it.
‫أنا متأكدة من ذلك.‬
He was there.
‫كان هناك.‬
Attendees of the ceremony reported that
‫ذكر الحاضرون في الحفل‬
just before the fire, you told everyone to evacuate immediately.
‫أنك قبل الحريق مباشرةً‬ ‫طلبت من الجميع أن يخلوا المكان فورًا.‬
Why did you say that?
‫لماذا قلت ذلك؟‬
You must have realized something was about to happen.
‫لا بد أنك أدركت أن ثمة ما سيحدث.‬
Isn't that right, Mr. Schuwald?
‫أليس هذا صحيحًا يا سيد "شوفالد"؟‬
I think that's about enough.
‫أظن أن هذا يكفي.‬
Also, do you know this man?
‫هل تعرف هذا الرجل أيضًا؟‬
Can you see it if I hold it this close?
‫أيمكنك رؤيته إن قرّبت الصورة هكذا؟‬
This man attempted to assassinate you.
‫حاول هذا الرجل أن يغتالك.‬
Some witnesses say he was at the library.
‫يقول بعض الشهود إنه كان في المكتبة.‬
According to witnesses, they say that this man saved people.
‫يقول الشهود إن هذا الرجل أنقذ الناس.‬
That's enough. I'm putting an end to this.
‫هذا يكفي. يجب أن تتوقف.‬
If he remembers anything, call me right away.
‫إن تذكّر شيئًا، فاتصل بي فورًا.‬
One more thing.
‫ثمة أمر آخر.‬
Do you know the whereabouts of your secretary, Johan Liebert?
‫هل تعرف مكان سكرتيرك "يوهان ليبرت"؟‬
That's enough! Get out now!
‫هذا يكفي! اخرج فورًا!‬
He's gone completely senile.
‫لقد تمكن الخرف منه تمامًا.‬
After going through something like that at his age, it's no wonder.
‫لا عجب في ذلك بعد الذي تعرّض له‬ ‫وهو في مثل هذا العمر.‬
I guess this is the end of the road for the financial kingpin,
‫أرى أن هذه هي نهاية القطب المالي،‬
the Vampire of Bavaria.
‫مصاص دماء "بافاريا".‬
-No, it's not. -What?
‫- لم تحلّ نهايته بعد.‬ ‫- ماذا؟‬
I could tell from his eyes that he understood everything.
‫تبيّنت من نظرة عينيه أنه فهم كل ما يجري.‬
Really?
‫حقًا؟‬
Let's talk to some of the other witnesses.
‫لنتحدث إلى بعض الشهود الآخرين.‬
Do you have a list of the victims?
‫هل لديك قائمة بأسماء الضحايا؟‬
Yes, I do.
‫نعم، لديّ.‬
What do you think is going on anyway?
‫ما الذي يحصل برأيك؟‬
I mean, witnesses said that someone who looks like Tenma rescued people.
‫قال الشهود‬ ‫إن شخصًا يشبه "تينما" أنقذ الناس.‬
Do you think it could be a case of multiple personalities?
‫أتظن أنها قضية شخص‬ ‫مصاب بانفصام في الشخصية؟‬
"Nina"…
‫"نينا"…‬
"Nina Fortner."
‫"نينا فورتنر".‬
Does that name ring a bell?
‫هل يبدو هذا الاسم مألوفًا؟‬
Nina Fortner was released this morning.
‫خرجت "نينا فورتنر" في صباح اليوم.‬
The address on the police record was fake. What's in the hospital records?
‫العنوان المدوّن في سجلات الشرطة مزيّف.‬ ‫ما العنوان المسجّل في سجلات المستشفى؟‬
Hold on. I'll look it up.
‫أمهلاني لحظة. سأبحث عنه.‬
Nina Fortner.
‫"نينا فورتنر".‬
Same name as the daughter of the Fortners who was killed in Heidelberg.
‫إنه اسم ابنة آل "فورتنر"‬ ‫اللذين قُتلا في "هايدلبرغ".‬
She's currently missing.
‫وهي مفقودة حاليًا.‬
Thank you for sharing such a painful story with me.
‫شكرًا لمشاركتك هذه القصة المؤلمة معي.‬
It matches perfectly
‫إنها تتوافق تمامًا‬
with the story Tenma told me about what's happened the last ten years.
‫مع القصة التي أخبرني بها "تينما"‬ ‫عمّا حدث في السنوات العشر الماضية.‬
Tenma?
‫"تينما"؟‬
That's right. He came here in his investigation of these cases.
‫هذا صحيح.‬ ‫قاده تقصّيه عن تلك القضايا إلى هنا.‬
He soon left so he could assassinate Johan.
‫سرعان ما غادر ليتمكن من اغتيال "يوهان".‬
I believe Tenma was at the library that day to carry out
‫أعتقد أن " تينما" كان في المكتبة‬ ‫في ذلك اليوم‬
his assassination attempt.
‫لتنفيذ محاولة الاغتيال.‬
That's why I went there.
‫لذلك ذهبت إلى هناك.‬
But then there was that fire.
‫لكنني وجدت أن حريقًا قد اندلع.‬
Now I don't know if Tenma was even there, let alone Johan.
‫ما عدت أعرف الآن ما إن كان "تيمنا"‬ ‫قد ذهب إلى هناك، ناهيك عن "يوهان".‬
Listen to me, Nina. Stop going after Johan.
‫اسمعيني يا "نينا". كفّي عن ملاحقة "يوهان".‬
He's more than you can handle.
‫إنه أخطر من أن تتمكني من التعامل معه.‬
I'd agree that the police aren't much help.
‫أوافقك الرأي في أن الشرطة غير مجدية.‬
We need to proceed slowly and carefully in this fight.
‫يجب أن نتمهل ونحذر‬ ‫في تحرّكاتنا بشأن هذا الصراع.‬
Someday, the truth will come out.
‫ستظهر الحقيقة يومًا ما.‬
Don't you worry. We'll help you.
‫لا تقلقي. سنساعدك.‬
You must be exhausted.
‫لا بد أنك مرهقة.‬
Why don't you rest here for the time being?
‫لم لا ترتاحين هنا حاليًا؟‬
-He was there. -What?
‫- كان هناك.‬ ‫- ماذا؟‬
He was definitely there at the library then.
‫كان في المكتبة آنذاك مما لا شك فيه.‬
Tenma was there.
‫كان "تينما" هناك.‬
You should eat.
‫يجب أن تأكلي.‬
Thank you, Dieter.
‫أشكرك يا "ديتر".‬
Those are Kaiser rolls.
‫إنهما شطيرتان.‬
I've put roasted ham and Gouda cheese on them.
‫وضعت فيهما لحم خنزير مشوي وجبن "غودا".‬
That's Tenma's favorite.
‫إنها الشطيرة المفضلة لـ"تينما".‬
I appreciate this.
‫أنا ممتنة لك.‬
-It's delicious. -Really?
‫- إنها لذيذة.‬ ‫- حقًا؟‬
Yes. Good food makes me feel better.
‫أجل. تتحسّن معنوياتي‬ ‫عند تناول الطعام الشهي.‬
Tenma always said that too.
‫دائمًا ما يتحدث "تينما"‬ ‫بمثل هذا الكلام أيضًا.‬
I'd like to see him.
‫أود مقابلته.‬
I'd like to see Tenma.
‫أود مقابلة "تينما".‬
Me too.
‫وأنا أيضًا.‬
The weather's looking nice again.
‫يبدو الطقس جميلًا اليوم أيضًا.‬
I have an idea. How about we take a trip when you're better?
‫لديّ فكرة.‬ ‫ما رأيك في أن نخرج في رحلة عندما تتحسن؟‬
A trip to Asia might be nice.
‫قد يعجبك أن نخرج في رحلة إلى "آسيا".‬
It would be a good change of pace.
‫قد يكون هذا تغييرًا جيدًا.‬
You know, you should really take it easy more often now.
‫يجب أن تترفق بنفسك أكثر الآن.‬
Dad, you've worked long and hard enough already.
‫أنت قد عملت بجد واجتهاد لوقت طويل يا أبي.‬
A bridge…
‫جسر…‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
Three frogs…
‫ثلاثة ضفادع…‬
What's that? What are you trying to say?
‫ماذا قلت؟ ما الذي تحاول قوله؟‬
There were three frogs…
‫ثمة ثلاثة ضفادع…‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
In his eyes…
‫في عينيه…‬
His eyes?
‫عينيه؟‬
I could see hell…
‫رأيت الجحيم…‬
in his eyes.
‫في عينيه.‬
I could see hell in the eyes of a living human.
‫رأيت الجحيم في عيني إنسان حي.‬
Karl.
‫"كارل".‬
Yes?
‫نعم؟‬
I have something I want you to tell a certain man.
‫ثمة ما أريدك أن تقوله لشخص ما.‬
Okay.
‫حسنًا.‬
The man is waiting in Dresden.
‫ينتظر الرجل في "دريسدن".‬
In Dresden? What should I tell him?
‫في "دريسدن"؟ بم أخبره؟‬
Okay.
‫حسنًا.‬
So you want me to send that message to the man waiting in Dresden, right?
‫أتريدني أن أعطي هذه الرسالة‬ ‫للرجل الذي ينتظر في "دريسدن"؟‬
Do you want me to do it now?
‫أتريد أن أفعل هذا الآن؟‬
All right. I'll leave immediately.
‫حسنًا. سأغادر في الحال.‬
Karl.
‫"كارل".‬
Your mother,
‫والدتك،‬
she hated me, didn't she?
‫كرهتني، أليس كذلك؟‬
No. She didn't hate you.
‫لا. لم تكرهك.‬
Karl, when you return from Dresden,
‫عندما تعود من "دريسدن" يا "كارل"،‬
will you stay with me?
‫هل ستبقى معي؟‬
Yes.
‫نعم.‬
I'm scared.
‫أنا خائفة.‬
Scared of what?
‫ممّ تخافين؟‬
I'm not sure why, but I'm very scared.
‫لست متأكدة من السبب ولكنني أشعر بخوف شديد.‬
Try to remember.
‫حاولي أن تتذكري.‬
But take your time. Don't push yourself.
‫لكن خذي وقتك. لا تضغطي على نفسك.‬
A town out of a fairytale.
‫بلدة من الخيال.‬
A fairytale town? Where is it?
‫بلدة من الخيال؟ أين هي؟‬
What did you feel when you looked at this book?
‫بم شعرت عندما طالعت هذا الكتاب؟‬
Tell me whatever comes to mind. Anything at all.
‫أخبريني بما يخطر في بالك. أي شيء.‬
Dr. Gillen, be careful.
‫انتبه يا د. "غيلن".‬
Just a little longer.
‫سأستمر لبعض الوقت.‬
Stop, please!
‫توقف أرجوك!‬
Three frogs…
‫ثلاثة ضفادع…‬
There were three frogs.
‫ثمة ثلاثة ضفادع.‬
There were three frogs?
‫ثلاثة ضفادع؟‬
What are you talking about?
‫عمّ تتحدثين؟‬
The picture…
‫الصورة…‬
A picture?
‫صورة؟‬
Do you mean they're in this picture book that made Johan faint?
‫أتقصدين أنها في هذا الكتاب المصوّر‬ ‫الذي تسبب في إغماء "يوهان"؟‬
There's no drawing of three frogs anywhere in that book.
‫ما من رسمة لثلاثة ضفادع في ذلك الكتاب.‬
Where did you see that picture?
‫أين رأيت تلك الصورة؟‬
That's enough.
‫هذا يكفي.‬
That's all for today.
‫لنكتف بهذا القدر اليوم.‬
Okay.
‫حسنًا.‬
It was a mistake to hope that Inspector Lunge of the BKA would help us.
‫أخطأنا بأن أملنا في أن يساعدنا "لونغي"‬ ‫من مكتب الشرطة الجنائية الفيدرالية.‬
You're right. I think we should change our strategy too.
‫أنت محق. أظن أنه يجدر بنا‬ ‫أن نغيّر استراتيجيتنا.‬
Next time we bring evidence to the police,
‫في المرة المقبلة‬ ‫التي نقدّم فيها دليلًا للشرطة،‬
we should speak directly with his superiors.
‫يجب أن نتحدث مباشرةً إلى رؤسائهم.‬
And it should only be evidence that we've taken the time
‫ويجب أن يكون دليلًا قد تحققنا منه باستفاضة.‬
But how much time should we take?
‫لكن كم سنستغرق من وقت؟‬
The information we have on Johan now is vague and there's far too little.
‫معلوماتنا عن "يوهان" حاليًا‬ ‫غير واضحة ولا نعرف إلا القليل.‬
I'm sure that the man Johan worked for, Schuwald, has some information.
‫أنا متأكد من أن "شوفالد"،‬ ‫الذي عمل لديه "يوهان"، يعرف بعض المعلومات.‬
But he's still not taking visitors. What about his son, Karl?
‫لكن لا تزال الزيارات ممنوعة عنه.‬ ‫ماذا عن ابنه، "كارل"؟‬
He left for somewhere two days ago, but I can't reach him.
‫غادر إلى مكان قبل يومين،‬ ‫لكن لا يسعني الوصول إليه.‬
It's nothing concrete,
‫إنه ليس دليلًا ملموسًا،‬
but some of the witnesses said that an Asian man helped them escape.
‫لكن عددًا من الشهود أدلوا‬ ‫بأن ثمة أسيوي ساعدهم على الهروب.‬
But if Tenma's fingerprints are found on the sniper rifle discovered at the scene,
‫لكن إن عُثر على بصمات "تينما"‬ ‫على بندقية القنص في مسرح الجريمة،‬
no number of witness statements will save him.
‫فلن يساعده أي عدد كان من إفادات الشهود.‬
How long should we wait?
‫إلى متى يجب أن ننتظر؟‬
There's no more time!
‫ما من وقت!‬
When the truth becomes clear and the police take action,
‫عند اتضاح الحقيقة وتحرّك الشرطة،‬
by that time…
‫حينها…‬
Tenma will…
‫سيكون "تينما"…‬
Nina.
‫"نينا".‬
I'm sorry.
‫أنا آسفة.‬
Nina, I understand very well how you feel.
‫أتفهم شعورك يا "نينا".‬
I lost a close friend of mine, Richard, in all of this.
‫أنا فقدت صديقي المقرّب "ريتشارد"‬ ‫في خضم تلك الأحداث.‬
He had a bright future ahead of him.
‫كان له مستقبل واعد.‬
But Johan cut his future short.
‫لكن "يوهان" قد أنهى له مستقبله.‬
I am not giving up. Never!
‫لن أستسلم. أبدًا.‬
Okay, let's eat.
‫حسنًا، لنأكل.‬
Three frogs…
‫ثلاثة ضفادع…‬
Like a town out of a fairy tale…
‫بلدة أشبه ببلدان الخيال…‬
I know what it is!
‫أعرف ما تكون!‬
Dieter…
‫"ديتر"…‬
I'm going with you.
‫سأرافقك.‬
Don't be silly. You can't go.
‫لا تكن سخيفًا. لا يمكنك مرافقتي.‬
You stay here. Understand?
‫ابق هنا. مفهوم؟‬
Tell Dr. Reichwein thank you for taking care of me.
‫أبلغ د. "راشفاين" بامتناني له‬ ‫على اعتنائه بي.‬
Goodbye.
‫مع السلامة.‬
Dieter!
‫"ديتر"!‬
I want to see him.
‫أريد أن أراه.‬
I want to see Tenma!
‫أريد أن أرى "تينما".‬
DRESDEN (SAXONY)
‫"(دريسدن)، (ساكسونيا)"‬
Day three and still nothing.
‫مضت ثلاثة أيام ولم يحدث شيئًا.‬
I'm supposed to wait in the square at the station, but this place is huge.
‫يُفترض بي أن أنتظر في ميدان المحطة،‬ ‫لكن هذا المكان ضخم.‬
I don't think I'll be able to meet the man you told me about, Father.
‫أظن أنه لن يسعني مقابلة الرجل‬ ‫الذي أخبرتني عنه يا أبي.‬
Karl.
‫"كارل".‬
You're Karl, aren't you?
‫أنت "كارل"، أليس كذلك؟‬
Who are you?
‫من تكون؟‬
The man who was attempting to assassinate your father.
‫الرجل الذي حاول اغتيال والدك.‬
Isn't that what the police told you?
‫أليس هذا ما قالته الشرطة لك؟‬
Yes.
‫نعم.‬
I've been watching you from that building for three days.
‫أنا أراقبك من ذلك المبنى منذ ثلاثة أيام.‬
It appears the police aren't tailing you.
‫يبدو أن الشرطة لا تتعقبك.‬
Give me the message.
‫أعطني الرسالة.‬
Hang in there. We're almost out.
‫اصمد. كدنا نخرج.‬
Hurry up and get out. The police will be here soon.
‫أسرع في الخروج من هنا.‬ ‫ستصل الشرطة بعد قليل.‬
But…
‫لكن…‬
Go to Dresden. Wait in the train station square.
‫اذهب إلى "دريسدن". ميدان محطة القطار.‬
My son Karl will bring you a message.
‫سيعطيك "كارل" ابني رسالة.‬
Give me the message.
‫أعطني الرسالة.‬
This is it.
‫هذه هي.‬
"Cedok Bridge.The Three Frogs"?
‫"جسر (تشيدوك). الضفادع الثلاثة"؟‬
My father also told me this.
‫وأخبرني والدي بالتالي أيضًا.‬
"If the monster you are chasing has a twin…"
‫"إن كان للوحش الذي تطارده توأم…"‬
The twins' mother is alive and living in Prague.
‫فوالدة التوأم حيّة وتعيش في "براغ".‬